http://www.bradshawfoundation.com/privacy_policy.php

Tweet
At the Bradshaw Foundation, we have a duty to protect your privacy and all personal data that is collected during your interaction with our website. Please ensure that you keep up to date with the information on this page, as it is subject to change in accordance with new legislation and directives. We only collect information about you that is required to process your order to give you the best possible service.
This Privacy Policy will explain what data we collect from you, how we use that data, who can see your data and how you can access/change the personal data we hold.
What Information Do We Collect From You?
The Bradshaw Foundation may ask you to input and collect the following information during the ordering process on this website: Customer Name, Billing Address, Shipping Address, Telephone Number, and Email Address.
In addition to this we also have a contact form which if used collects your name, email, country, organisation and message text.
When you enter payment information, this is not held by The Bradshaw Foundation, but collected by our Third Party payment processor PayPal in a secure manner (see Who Can See Your Information?).
How Is Your Information Used?
The Bradshaw Foundation may use your information to:
Process a payment;
Process an order;
Deliver or redeliver an order;
Resolve an enquiry related to an existing or potential order;
Please rest assured that your privacy is extremely important to us so we will always keep your details secure, and we will NEVER use your data for marketing purposes, and will NEVER pass your data to a third party for marketing purposes.
Who Can See Your Information?
The Bradshaw Foundation will not sell or rent your information to Third Parties for marketing purposes. We do however work with a small number of Third Party organisations to help us deliver some customer services, some of which have limited access to your data. We may pass your information to these Third Party service providers for the purpose of providing services to your behalf. Examples include sending emails, processing payments and targeted advertisements on social media. The information shared will be that which is only relevant to the task at hand. Third Parties cannot use or share your information for any other purpose than to carry out what The Bradshaw Foundation has requested them to do and are required to keep your data secure. Please see below for a list of our Third Party partners, a brief rundown of the services they provide and links to their own privacy policies.
Third Parties who work on behalf of, or in association with, The Bradshaw Foundation:
PayPal
Payment processor
Privacy policy https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full
Privacy policy from 25th May 2018 https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-prev
Please rest assured that your privacy is extremely important to us so we will always keep your details secure, and we will NEVER use your data for marketing purposes, and will NEVER pass your data to a third party for marketing purposes.
Recording Information
PayPal sales invoices, messages sent through our contact us form and other messages sent through social media accounts are archived and can be referred to in order to resolve issues that may arise during ordering or with customer aftercare.
Sales invoices may need to be kept for up to 7 years in order for The Bradshaw Foundation to retrospectively provide tax information to HMRC (please see Right To Erasure).
Our Security Precautions
This website has a valid SSL security certificate which means that any information you enter into the site is private. For more information, click on the lock symbol that appears next to the URL of the website which will give you the full information.
Cookies
Cookies are tiny text files in your browser that can be sent from an organisations website and saved onto your computer when you visit a website for the first time. These text files typically contain two pieces of information: a unique user ID and the site name. Each time you visit a website that holds cookies, your computer checks its system to see if it has cookies from that website already saved, therefore recognising if you have visited the website before. The Bradshaw Foundation uses cookies to track user visits, therefore analysing data such as the numbers of returning customers, customer location (by country or region) and recording how long customers stay on our website. Cookies DO NOT identify you as an individual, but simply track your browsing patterns which helps us to target our advertisements more accurately to our customers. The viewing of the website and browsing of the website automatically requires you to accept our Cookies policy. When you enter into a transaction with the company you automatically accept the trading terms and conditions as enclosed. You have the option within your browser to disable cookies, which you can do by following the specific browser instructions.
Cookies are stored in your browser which you can usually modify to prevent this happening. If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should log onto our website and use the contact us form on our "Contact Us" page or email us boilerplate@bradshawfoundation.com
Right To Erasure
In accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulations 2018, you have the right to request that The Bradshaw Foundation erases all personal data that we hold on you with immediate effect. In some cases, The Bradshaw Foundation may have to retain certain vital information if we can prove that your data is needed to carry out other vital business processes, for example, filing tax returns (where we will need to retain sales invoices).
Links To Other Websites
The Bradshaw Foundation website may contain links to external organisations. Please be aware that by clicking a link to an external source, our privacy policy no longer applies whilst you are on that new site. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies that our linked websites adhere to and recommend that you read the policy of that site to keep yourself informed.
Data Breaches
The Bradshaw Foundation has a duty to report any breach of personal data from our database or our Third Party databases to all relevant people and the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) if it is apparent that personal data has been stolen or misused, within 72 hours of the incident.
Policy Review
The Bradshaw Foundation will keep this policy up to date in accordance with the law and new regulations. This policy was last updated 19/06/2018.
Follow the Bradshaw Foundation on social media for news & updates
Follow the Bradshaw Foundationon social media for news & updates
Follow @BradshawFND
Tweet
Follow the Bradshaw Foundation on social media for news & updates
Follow the Bradshaw Foundationon social media for news & updates
Follow @BradshawFND
Tweet
Homepage • About • Latest News • iShop • Book Review • Site Map • Donate • Facebook • Twitter • Contact
Homepage • About • Latest News • iShopBook Review • Site Map • DonateFacebook • Twitter • Contact
Homepage • About • Latest News • iShop • Book ReviewSite Map • Donate • Facebook • Twitter • Contact
If you have enjoyed visiting this websiteplease consider adding a link © Bradshaw Foundation
Life in Rock Art (PDF)
America's Oldest Art?
When & Who Built It?
How Was It Built?
